When you run Claude Code, you can enter in a forward
Claude Code を実行すると、フォワード
slash and see a bunch of commands that are built into Claude Code
スラッシュを入力して、Claude Code に組み込まれている
by default. In addition to these default commands,
コマンドをたくさん見ることができます。これらのデフォルトコマンドに加えて、
you can easily add your own custom commands as well. Custom
独自のカスタムコマンドも簡単に追加できます。カスタム
commands are useful for automating repetitive tasks that
コマンドは、頻繁に実行することになる繰り返しタスクを自動化するのに役立ちます。
you find yourself running frequently. Let me show you an example of how
作成方法の例をお見せしましょう。プロジェクトディレクトリ内で、
to make one. Inside of my project directory,
.Claude フォルダを見つけます。その中に
I'm going to find the .Claude folder. Inside there, I'll
commands という名前の新しいディレクトリを作成します。次に
make a new directory called commands. And then inside
その中に audit.md という新しいファイルを作成します。
that, I'll make a new file called audit.md.
作成するファイルの名前（この場合は audit）は、
The name of the file that we create, in this case audit,
最終的に実行するコマンドの名前になります。このコマンドの
is going to be the name of the command we eventually run. The
目標は、このプロジェクトにインストールされているすべての依存関係を監査し、
goal of this command is going to be to audit all the different dependencies
脆弱性があれば更新し、その後
that have been installed into this project, update them
テストを実行して、何も壊れていないことを確認することです。
if there are any vulnerabilities, and then run
コマンドファイルを作成したら、Claude Code を再起動します。
tests to make sure that nothing actually broke. Once
再起動を忘れないでください。Claude Code を再度開く際には、
you have created the command file, you'll then restart Claude
スラッシュ audit と入力します。これにより、
Code. Don't forget to restart it. When you reopen
作成したばかりのコマンドが表示されます。これを実行すると、
Claude Code, put in slash audit. This
この場合、Claude に要求したことを正確に実行します。コマンドを実行し、
will then display the command that you just created. You can then
脆弱なパッケージがないかを確認し、必要に応じて修正し、
run this, and in this case, it will do exactly what we ask Claude
その後テストを実行します。コマンドは引数を受け取ることもできます。
to do. It'll run a command, see if there are any vulnerable
例をお見せしましょう。write test という別のコマンドを作成します。
packages, fix them if necessary, and then run
このコマンドを実行するたびに、プロジェクト内の特定のファイルに
tests. Commands can also receive arguments. Let
対するテストを作成したいと思います。コマンドテキスト内で、
me show you an example. I'm going to make another command called write
ドル記号 arguments というプレースホルダーを入力します。
test. Whenever I run this command, I want to have
コマンドを実行する際に、ファイルへのパスを渡すと、
some tests created for a very particular file inside
そのパスがドル記号 arguments に挿入されます。
my project. Inside of the command text, I'm going
これで Claude Code を再度再起動し、
to put in a placeholder of dollar sign arguments. Whenever
write test コマンドを実行できます。ここで明確にしておきますが、
I run the command, if I pass in a path to a file, that
渡す引数はファイルパスである必要はありません。
path will be inserted at dollar sign arguments.
渡したい任意の文字列にすることができます。したがって、
So now I can restart Claude Code again and then execute
特定のフォルダ内のファイルに対するテストをカジュアルに依頼することもあります。
the write test command. Now, to be clear,
Claude にどこを探すべきかの指示を少しだけ与えます。
the arguments we pass in don't have to be a file
ですので、Claude Code を再度再起動し、
path. It can be any string we want to pass in. So
write test コマンドを実行します。さて、明確にするために、
I might casually ask for tests for a file in some particular
渡す引数はファイルパスである必要はありません。
folder, giving Claude just a little bit of direction on
渡したい任意の文字列にすることができます。したがって、
where to look.
特定のフォルダ内のファイルに対するテストをカジュアルに依頼することもあります。